{
    "subject": "resource/Rich_Relations_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Ralph_Forbes",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Rich Relations' stars Ralph Forbes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8396149277687073,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Ralph Forbes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.786068320274353,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Rich Relations'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6852015852928162,
            "question": "What other films has Ralph Forbes appeared in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5481709241867065,
            "question": "Is Ralph Forbes known for any particular role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5154899954795837,
            "question": "Name an actor who appeared in the film 'Rich Relations'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44715213775634766,
            "question": "What is Ralph Forbes's most famous role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3823472857475281,
            "question": "When was the film 'Rich Relations' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38022756576538086,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Rich Relations' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31494882702827454,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the director of 'Rich Relations'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30091196298599243,
            "question": "Were there any sequels or remakes of 'Rich Relations'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Rich Relations' stars Ralph Forbes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3523_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the director of 'Rich Relations'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3523_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Rich Relations' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3523_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'Rich Relations' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3523_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3523_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information indicates that Ralph Forbes played a role in the film \"Rich Relations,\" which supports the statement that the film \"Rich Relations\" stars Ralph Forbes."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}